MYKOLA SHCHYPAILO

QA ENGINEER

SUMMARY

I'm a QA Engineer with deep experience in both Backend and Frontend testing which has been applied in development of large international projects.

My confidence and expertise enable me to identify and maximize my contributions effectively.

- +38-067-987-67-67
- kolyakol8787@gmail.com
- **9** Ukraine, Kiev

LANGUAGE

- ENGLISH B2
- UKRANIAN NATIVE

SOFT SKILLS

- COMMUNICATIVE
- RESPONSIBLE
- CRITICAL-THINKING
- ADAPTABILITY
- HARD-WORKER
- RESULT-ORIENTED
- TEAMWORK

EXPERIENCE

QA Automation Engineer Extrawest (ICASA, Electriqua)

Dec 2023 - to present

- API tests automation using Java, Rest Assured;
- Mobile tests automation using Android Studio, Appium;
- Manual testing using Postman;
- Creating API/Mobile framework from scratch;
- Optimization Ci/CD process;
- Creating and working with documentation;

QA Automation Engineer Project under NDA (Binary options)

Nov 2022 - Dec 2023

- Ui tests automation using Java, Selenide;
- API tests automation using Rest Assured, Postman;
- Working with documentation;
- Optimization QA process;
- Performance testing using Gatling;

QA Automation Engineer EXIST.UA

Mar 2021 - Nov 2022

- Ui tests automation using Java: Selenium, Maven, TestNG;
- Working with documentation;
- Performance testing using JMeter;
- Security testing using OWASP ZAP

EDUCATION

Kiev University of Law of the National Academy of Sciences of Ukraine, Kiev

Bachelor Sep 2014 – May 2019

TECH SKILLS

- Java
- Maven, Gradle, TestNG, JUnit, Lombok, MySQL
- Selenium, Selenide
- Android Studio, Appium
- Postman, Rest Assured, JDBC, Jackson, Docker
- VCS: Git (GitHub, GitLab)
- Jenkins, Jira, Allure, Testomat, TestRail
- Cypress, Playwright, BStack
- JMeter, Gatling, OWASP ZAP